<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PUBG Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="admob_interstetial_ad">ca-app-pub-6803138759314501/6828209604</string>



    <string name="erangle">Erangel is the base map for the game. An 8x8 km map dotted with small
        outcroppings of buildings, the distance between major landmarks necessitates the use of
        vehicles to move between areas. As the game continues, the map area will be restricted to
        a smaller and smaller play area. A red circle will appear on the map from time to time,
        marking an area for offshore artillery to bombard. Erangel has varying weather,
        sometimes affecting visibility and requiring a change in tactics.
        Cities and the local military base have plenty of decent loot.</string>


    <string name="miramar">Miramar offers unique terrain and dense urban areas.
        With an island to the south east home to a prison and smaller villages,
        the entire area is cut off from the west and north-east by enormous
        canyons and mountains, with a looming metal wall to the north keeping
        outsiders out, and players in. Miramar will create a new Battle Royale
        experience where the old strategies from Erangel may no longer
        work and new tactics are required.</string>



    <string name="sanhok">Sanhok is the first map that the art team of PUBG Corp
        visited a location specifically for world art development. By physically
        being in the jungles and mountains in a humid Asian country, it not only
        made them imagine what the new map will play like, but they felt the breeze,
        smelled the air and heard the sounds. All of these experiences are helping the
        team create a unique map experience.
        The map is inspired by a wide variety of islands in Thailand and the Philippines,
        the PUBG Art team; comprised of Technical Artists, Concept Artists and 3D Environment
        Artists, they took photos (Photogrammetry) to capture the island then transfer that to
        the game engine to design Sanhok</string>

    <string name="vikendi">An isolated Northern resort island in the shadow of Mount Kreznic,
        Vikendi was home to a wide variety of attractions, businesses and villages. Vikendi
        is enveloped in dense/thick forest and another aspect of the island is its warm
        Mediterranean coastline and snowy mountains in the central area of the map.
        Tourists can look to the future from the Cosomodrome, travel back to the past
        and walk with the giants at the prehistoric Dino Park, visit the aging Castle
        or even take a tour of the winery. Vikendi is as beautiful as it is dangerous and
        Survivors treading these bitter cold lands will have to watch their backs even more
        closely, as the fresh snow is perfect for leaving behind footprints! With snow and the
        footprints that you leave behind or other players leave behind, the hunter becomes the
        hunted. The days are long on Vikendi, but it won’t be long before the sun sets and the
        auroras fill the moonlit skies.
        The map is inspired by Slovenia to create the visual design of the map </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>



</resources>
